Finding Aid for International Board on Books for Young People
Clarke Historical Library
- International Board on Books for Young People, Dossiers of Award Nominees
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Hevier, Daniel,2014 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Kaaberbøl, Lene [Kaaverboel, Lene-spelled thus in file], flashdrive,2014 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Kim, Jin-Kyung [Kim, Jin-gyloung],2014 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Kovač, Polonca,2014 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Kunnas, Kirsi,2014 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Lieshout, Ted van,2014 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Madouvalou, Sophia, 3 CDs,2014 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Mourlevat, Jean-Claude,2014 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Murādī Kirmānī, Hūshang [LC authority spelling], 3 CDs,2014 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Nurugizi, Sevinj,2014 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Oppel, Kenneth,2014 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Pervik, Anio,2014 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Pitzorno, Bianca, CD,2014 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Pressler Mirjam, CD,2014 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Ramos, Maria Cristina,2014 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Santos, Joel Rufino dos,2014 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Sortland, Bjørn,2014 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Tarrado, Antonio,2014 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Torseter, Øyvind,2014 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Uehashi, Nahoko, CD,2014 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Ural, Serpil, CD,2014 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Welsh, Renate,2014 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Wheatley, Nadia, CD,2014 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Wilson, Jacqueline,2014 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Woodson, Jacqueline,2014 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Yang, Hongying, CD,2014 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Albertine,2014 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Béha, Philippe,2014 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Berner, Rotraut Susanne,2014 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Brooks, Ron, CD,2014 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Burningham, John,2014 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Ceylan, Saadet, CD,2014 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Cneut, Carll, CD,2014 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Collier, Bryan,2014 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Han, Byoung-Ho [Han, Hyoung-ho],2014 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Isol, CD,2014 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Junaković, Svjetlan,2014 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Katayama, Ken,2014 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Krapivin, Vladislav,2014 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Lindström, Eva,2014 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Lynch, P. J.,2014 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Negrin, Fabian, CD,2014 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Oleǐnikov, Igor [Olynikov, Igor], CD,2014 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Pardi, Charlotte,2014 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Pētersons, Reinis,2014 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Place, François,2014 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Sottler, Alenka,2014 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Stamatiadi, Daniela, CD,2014 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Tornqvist, Marit,2014 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Uchnár, Peter,2014 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Vuori, Pekka,2014 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Wolfsgruber, Linda,2014 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Xiong, Liang [also known as Xiong, Kim],2014 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Zambala, Javiar, CD only,2014 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - (Oversized Custom-made Maroon Box decorated with red, white and blue ape, in Legal-size Folder) Dossiers of Illustrator’s Award Nominees, Mello, Roger,2014 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - List of Award Winners, Nominees, July Check List, Notes,2016 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Alpöge, Gülçin, CD,2016 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Bringsværd Tor Åge,2016 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Cao, Wenxuan, CD,2016 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Carminati, Chiara, CD,2016 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Colasanti, Marina,2016 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Cowley, Joy,2016 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Devetach, Laura,2016 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Dikaiou, Eleni,2016 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Dubosarsky, Ursula,2016 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Fernández Paz, Agustín, 2 CDs,2016 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Fombelle, Timothée de,2016 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Gavran, Miro,2016 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Hevier, Daniel,2016 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Hohler, Franz,2016 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Jensen, Louis,2016 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Kadono, Eiko,2016 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Laird, Elizabeth,2016 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Lieshout, Ted van,2016 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Lowry, Lois (dossier currently unavailable),2016 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Makarović, Svetlana,2016 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Moeyaert, Bart,2016 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Nimr, Sonia,2016 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Oppel, Kenneth,2016 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Pressler, Mirjam, CD,2016 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Raud, Piret,2016 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Tobbala, Affaf, flash drive,2016 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Usachev, Andrey,2016 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers, Author’s Award Nominees: Welsh, Renate,2016 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Aisato, Lisa,2016 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Avci, Ferit,2016 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Bancroft, Bronwyn, CD,2016 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Berner, Rotraut Susanne, CD,2016 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Brøgger, Lilian, thumb drive,2016 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Delessert, Etienne,2016 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Federov, Mikhail,2016 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Fittipaldi, Ciça,2016 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Katayama, Ken, CD,2016 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Lee, Suzy,2016 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Lindstrom, Eva,2016 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Manček, Marjan,2016 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Pacheco, Gabriel,2016 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Paegle, Anita,2016 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Place, François,2016 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Prado, Miguelanxo [Miguel Anxo Prado Plana], CD,2016 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Pratt, Pierre,2016 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Rahimizadeh, Pejman, CD,2016 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Rascal,2016 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Rashka, Chris,2016 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Reuda, Claudia,2016 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Riddell, Chris,2016 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Sanna, Alessandro,2016 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Törnqvist,Marit,2016 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Uchnár, Peter,2016 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Varvarousi, Lida,2016 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Wolfsgruber, Linda,2016 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Zhu Chengliang, CD,2016 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - (Oversized Custom-made Blue Box:) Dossiers, Illustrator’s Award Nominees: Bianki [Bianchi, Diego Ariel], 3 CDs,2016 (Box 20)